This video will only focus on this metallic blue catsuit from Bright and Shiny.
And I'm going to try it on. It's a neck entry. It has no zipper in the back or the front.
That's going to be interesting.
Bright and Shiny is a Ukrainian brand who sent this to me and I can't wait to get into it
because I think the color looks really cool once I'm wearing it.
So, check it out.
it took me a little while because you know neck entry catsuit is never something to get into
really fast because you have to squeeze through this opening here the whole body luckily 0.25
millimeter latex gorge is really stretchy so I managed and what can I say I'm blown away by this
cut I mean it's called the anatomic cut catsuit and it's completely made to measure and I think
you can see that because it just it just fits so good. I'm amazed by the fit.
Enough with admiring the cut simply without saying something I'm going to
tell you a few facts. It is a thong pandy cut here so we have these seams here and
also in the back. Then leave the optical impression of a thong. So it's not just a
average catsuit cut but something special. I chose the following
configurations made to measure of course 0.25 millimeter gauge, fingerless
gloves, stirrups and the cups here and no zippers. So neither in the crotch nor in the
back nor in the front. Why no zippers? Because it just is a really different and snug fit without
zippers. So you have nothing that, yeah, disrupts the material with a different structure. And also
you can try and squeeze out the air and just, yeah, try to squeeze it out of the neck or the legs.
So it sits really, although I hate this expression, like a second skin. I love the fingerless gloss
and the stirrups as well because I ensure that the legs and arms are long enough with this option
and I also think that it's a cool look to have these thumb holes and it just looks instantly
more cozy with the thumb holes and also with the stirrups the legs can dry up so it's not going to
look too short and will always stay in place. And last but not least the cups. I think they really
enhance the whole fit and the whole figure it makes visually. Also when I
move to the side you can really see that my boobs are not pressed flat but they
have enough space and they look really good in this catsuit. So I love that
option also you can again try to press out the air around the boobs that it is
going to fit even better. I did not style it up yet so you could see the catsuit as it is
but it's time to gear up and do proper fetish styling. I simply put my Swedish
collar on top, I mean the collar and the cuffs. So now it's going to be really loud but I
think that it is not too too much so to say because the Swedish collars are black
with a bit of silver so it's really toned down and it fits the overall look. I
paired it with some black heels and of course have black fingernails and
toenails so that adds to the look as well and I think that is a really cool
fetish look that is not too aggressive so to say and I really like it. Back to
Brown and Shiny who made the suit. They're from Ukraine and they just launched a
new homepage so you should check it out. I have a discount code as well. I'll link it of course
and Bright and Shiny does not only do latex but they also have spandex items so have a look at
their shop. By the way I also do have a bodysuit from Bright and Shiny. I can show you a few
pictures. It is a metallic pewter and also 0.25 millimeters and yeah I think the pictures here
from the city harbor are really great still after all these years one last thing i want to try out
is adding this belt for the waist let's see if it matches the previous look okay obviously this one
screams fetish in your face now with the belt that's up to you what do you prefer with or
without belt or without swedish collar even leave a comment down below also i have to thank bright
and shiny for sending me this catsuit and for this cooperation i really enjoyed it and i really
enjoyed this cat suit so thanks does any one of you have a neck entry catsuit and do you have some
really cool tips to get into it so leave it in the comments my tip is just a lot of oil helps a lot
And with that, I'm done here for today. I hope you're having a nice time. See you in the next video. Bye!